Class of 1966 Records, 1962-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1966 Records
1962-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1966.
RG 80 UUID:da342c82-c905-4d0c-9c9c-6c0957231ecd
2 boxes (.63 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1966.
The Class of 1966 was the eighty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1966 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1966, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1966 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 1)
- Commencement Photographs 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1962-1963 (Box 2236, Folder 4)
- General 1964 (Box 2236, Folder 5)
- Groups 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1967-1976 (Box 2236, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2236, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1976-2006 (Box 2236, Folder 11)
- Reunions-40th Reunion Survey Results [compiled] 2006 (Box 2236, Folder 12)
- Who's Who 1962 (Box 2236, Folder 13)
- 25th Reunion Book (Box 2237, Folder 1)